{
    "subject": "resource/Zaman_(newspaper)",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "resource/Turkish_Language",
    "human_readable": "The language of Zaman (newspaper) is Turkish.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8262388706207275,
            "question": "What language does the Zaman newspaper use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6441295146942139,
            "question": "Is the Zaman newspaper published in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.538509726524353,
            "question": "Are there any other Turkish newspapers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.518981397151947,
            "question": "Which country is likely to have the Zaman newspaper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4554557800292969,
            "question": "What are some common topics covered in Turkish newspapers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3432348668575287,
            "question": "What can you infer about the target audience of the Zaman newspaper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26943230628967285,
            "question": "How might the language of a newspaper influence its content?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06461327522993088,
            "question": "What are some challenges faced by newspapers today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05921792984008789,
            "question": "Can you think of other examples of media published in specific languages?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02114788256585598,
            "question": "How has the internet changed the way people consume news?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of Zaman (newspaper) is Turkish.",
            "html": "dbpedia_906_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you think of other examples of media published in specific languages?",
            "html": "dbpedia_906_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some challenges faced by newspapers today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_906_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might the language of a newspaper influence its content?",
            "html": "dbpedia_906_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_906_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_906_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_906_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_906_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_906_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_906_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_906_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_906_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_906_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_906_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context explicitly states that \"ZAMAN Daily English Edition publishes Newspapers in these languages: Turkish,\" which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}